
### TABLE 1: Patient / Mobile Application
001	Login	Click the NgitiFy mobile application	Displays the Login page	shots=1	PASSED
002	Login/Forgot Password	Click Forgot Password button	Displays the Forgot Password page	shots=1	PASSED
003	Login/Forgot Password	Input the correct registered email, then click Send Verification Code button	System verifies the email and displays the OTP page	shots=1	PASSED
004	Login/Forgot Password	Input the correct OTP	System verifies the OTP and displays the Reset Password page	shots=1	PASSED
005	Login/Forgot Password	Input the new password and confirm new password, then click Reset Password button	System updates the password in the database and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
006	Login	Input the correct email and password, then click the Login button	System generates a token and displays the patient dashboard	shots=1	PASSED
007	Dashboard	Click the Home on the navigation menu	Displays the dashboard summary	shots=1	PASSED
008	Appointment Scheduling	Click Book Appointment button	Displays the appointment booking form	shots=1	PASSED
009	Appointment Scheduling	Select the available date and time, and the preferred procedure, then click Book Appointment button	System saves the appointment in the database and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
010	Appointment Scheduling	Click Reschedule Appointment button	Displays the appointment rescheduling form	shots=1	PASSED
011	Appointment Scheduling	Input the new appointment schedule, then click Reschedule button	System updates the appointment schedule in the database and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
012	Appointment Scheduling	Click Cancel Appointment button	System cancels the appointment in the database and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
013	AI Patient Care Companion/NgitiBot	Click NgitiBot floating button	Displays the NgitiBot conversation window	shots=1	PASSED
014	AI Patient Care Companion/NgitiBot	Input a patient care question, then click Send button	System processes the question and displays the NgitiBot response	shots=1	PASSED
015	AI Patient Care Companion/ / Dental Health Education	Click Dental Health Education button	Displays the dental health education materials	shots=1	PASSED
016	AI Patient Care Companion/ / Oral Health Management	Click Oral Health Management button	Displays the Oral Health Management page	shots=1	PASSED
017	AI Patient Care Companion/ / Predictive Visit	Click Predictive Visit button	Displays the Dentist Recommended Visit or the AI-generated recommendations for the next visit	shots=0	
018	Electronic Medical Record (EMR)/ / Medical and Dental History	Click Medical and Dental History	Displays the Medical and Dental History	shots=1	PASSED
019	Electronic Medical Record (EMR)/ / Treatment History	Click Treatment History	Displays the Treatment History	shots=1	PASSED
020	Electronic Medical Record (EMR)/ / Odontogram	Click Odontogram	Displays the patient odontogram	shots=1	PASSED
021	Electronic Medical Record (EMR)/ / Radiograph Images	Click Radiographs	Displays the uploaded / X-ray images	shots=1	PASSED
022	Notification	Click Notification button on the dashboard	Displays the Notifications page	shots=1	PASSED
023	Activity Logs	Click Activity Logs on the settings	Displays the Activity Logs page	shots=1	PASSED
024	Account Settings/ / View Profile	Click Profile	Displays the user profile information	shots=1	PASSED
025	Account Settings/ / Edit Profile	Click Edit button	Displays the edit profile form	shots=1	PASSED
026	Account Settings/ / Edit Profile	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System updates the profile information in the database, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
027	Account Settings/ / Change Password	Input a correct current password, new password, and confirm new password, then click Update Password button	System updates the password in the database, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
028	Logout	Click Logout button	System logs the user out and displays the Login page	shots=1	PASSED

### TABLE 2: Admin / Web Application
001	Login	Enter the correct URL	Displays the Login page	shots=1	PASSED
002	Login/Forgot Password	Click Forgot Password button	Displays the Forgot Password Page	shots=1	PASSED
003	Login/Forgot Password	Click Back to Login button	Displays the Login Page	shots=1	PASSED
004	Login/Forgot Password	Input correct registered email, then click Send Code button	System verifies the email and redirects to the OTP page	shots=1	PASSED
005	Login/Forgot Password	Input correct OTP, then click Verify button	System verifies the OTP and redirects to the reset password page	shots=1	PASSED
006	Login/Forgot Password	Input correct new password format matched with confirm new password, then click Reset Password button	System updates the password in the database and redirects to the login page	shots=1	PASSED
007	Login	Enter the correct email and password, then click Login button	System verifies the account and displays the administrator dashboard	shots=1	PASSED
008	Dashboard	Click the Dashboard from the sidebar	Displays the dashboard summary	shots=1	PASSED
009	Schedule Management	Click Schedule Management from the sidebar	Displays the schedule list	shots=1	PASSED
010	Schedule Management	Click View Schedule details	Displays the selected schedule details	shots=1	PASSED
011	Schedule Management/ / Edit Schedule Details	Click Edit Schedule Details button	Displays the edit schedule	shots=1	PASSED
012	Schedule Management/ / Edit Schedule Details	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System updates the schedule details information in the database, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
013	Schedule Management/ / Approve Schedule Entry	Click Approve Schedule Entry button	System approves the schedule entry, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
014	Schedule Management/ / Reject Schedule Entry	Click Reject Schedule Entry button	System rejects the schedule entry, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
015	User Accounts Management/ / Search User Accounts	Input a valid name or email	System searches the database and displays the matching user accounts	shots=1	PASSED
016	User Accounts Management/ / Create User Account	Click Add button	Displays the create user account form	shots=1	PASSED
017	User Accounts Management/ / Create User Account	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System saves the user account information in the database and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
018	User Accounts Management/ / Edit Use Account Details	Click Edit button	Displays the edit user account form	shots=1	PASSED
019	User Accounts Management/ / Edit Use Account Details	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System updates the user account information in the database, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
020	User Accounts Management/ / Deactivate User Account	Click Deactivate User Account button	System deactivates the user account, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
021	User Accounts Management/ / Archive User Account	Click Archive User Account button	System archives the user account, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
022	Patient EMR/ / Patient Profile	Click Patient Profile tab	Displays the selected patient profile	shots=1	PASSED
023	Patient EMR/ / Medical and Dental History	Click Medical and Dental History tab	Displays the selected patient medical and dental history	shots=1	PASSED
024	Patient EMR/ / Medical and Dental History	Click Edit button	Displays the edit medical and dental history form	shots=0	
025	Patient EMR/ / Medical and Dental History	Input all field completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System updates the medical and dental history information in the database, and displays a success message	shots=0	
026	Patient EMR/ / Treatment History	Click Treatment History tab	Displays the selected patient treatment history	shots=1	PASSED
027	Patient EMR/ / Treatment History	Click View Treatment Notes	Displays the selected treatment notes	shots=0	
028	Patient EMR/ / Digital Odontogram	Click Odontogram tab	Displays the selected patient digital odontogram	shots=1	PASSED
029	Patient EMR/ / Radiograph	Click Radiograph tab	Displays the selected patient X-ray	shots=1	PASSED
030	Patient EMR/ / Radiograph	Click X-ray Images	Display the X-ray summary notes	shots=1	PASSED
031	Branch Management and Expansion Analytics	Click Branch Management from the sidebar	Displays the clinic branches list	shots=1	PASSED
032	Branch Management and Expansion Analytics	Click View Individual Branch Details	Displays the selected branch analytics	shots=1	PASSED
033	Branch Management and Expansion Analytics	Click Edit Branch Details	Displays the edit branch details form	shots=1	PASSED
034	Branch Management and Expansion Analytics	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System updates the branch details in the database, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
035	Supply and Stock Monitoring	Click Supply & Stock Monitoring from the sidebar	Displays the Supply and Stock Monitoring page	shots=1	PASSED
036	Supply and Stock Monitoring	Click View Item Categories List	Displays the item categories list	shots=1	PASSED
037	Supply and Stock Monitoring/ / Update Item Stock Quantity	Click Update Item Stock Quantity button	Displays the edit item stock quantity form	shots=0	
038	Supply and Stock Monitoring/ / Update Item Stock Quantity	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System updates the item stock quantity information in the database, and displays a success message	shots=0	
039	Supply and Stock Monitoring/ / Add New Supply Entry	Click Add New Supply Entry button	Displays the create supply entry form	shots=1	PASSED
040	Supply and Stock Monitoring/ / Add New Supply Entry	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System saves the supply entry information in the database, and displays a success message	shots=0	
041	Supply and Stock Monitoring/ / Edit Item Details	Click Edit Item Details button	Displays the edit item details form	shots=0	
042	Supply and Stock Monitoring/ / Edit Item Details	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System updates the item details information in the database, and displays a success message	shots=0	
043	Supply and Stock Monitoring	Input a valid item name or code	System searches the database and displays matching supply items	shots=1	PASSED
044	Supply and Stock Monitoring	Click the In Stock, Low Stock, or Out of Stock filter	Displays supply items with the selected stock status	shots=1	PASSED
045	Branch Transfer Management	Click Transfer Branch button on selected patient	Display branch transfer form	shots=1	PASSED
046	Branch Transfer Management	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Transfer button	System updates the branch of the selected patient in the database, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
047	Database Backup	Click Database Backup from the sidebar	Displays the Database Backup page	shots=1	PASSED
048	Database Backup	Click Refresh button	System refreshes the database backup information	shots=1	PASSED
049	Database Backup	Click Create Backup Button	System creates the database backup, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
050	Database Backup	Click Download Available Backup button	System downloads the selected available database backup	shots=1	PASSED
051	Integrity Tools	Click the Integrity Tools from the sidebar	Displays the Integrity Tools page	shots=1	PASSED
052	Integrity Tools	Click Run Data Validation Scan button	System runs the data validation scan and displays the validation result	shots=1	PASSED
053	System Configuration	Click System Configuration from the sidebar	Displays the System Configuration page	shots=0	
054	System Configuration	Input the correct clinic name, contact number, email address, and address, then click Save Changes button	System updates the system configuration in the database, and displays a success message	shots=0	
055	Audit Trail	Click Audit Trail from the sidebar	Displays the Audit Trail page	shots=1	PASSED
056	Audit Trail	Input a valid audit log keyword on the search bar	System searches the database and displays matching system audit logs	shots=1	PASSED
057	Audit Trail	Click the user or date filter	Displays audit logs for the selected user or date	shots=1	PASSED
058	Notifications	Click Notifications from the sidebar	Displays the Notification page	shots=1	PASSED
059	Activity Logs	Click Activity Logs from the sidebar	Displays the Activity Logs page	shots=1	PASSED
060	Account Settings/ / View Profile	Click Profile tab	Displays the user profile information	shots=1	PASSED
061	Account Settings/ / Edit Profile	Click Edit Profile button	Displays the edit profile form	shots=1	PASSED
062	Account Settings/ / Edit Profile	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System updates the profile information in the database, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
063	Account Settings/ / Change Password	Click Change Password tab	Displays the Change Password page	shots=1	PASSED
064	Account Settings/ / Change Password	Input the correct current password, new password, and confirm new password, then click Save button	System updates the password in the database, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
065	Login/Sign out	Click �Logout� on the sidebar	System log user out, redirects to login page	shots=1	PASSED

### TABLE 3: Owner / Web Application
001	Login	Enter the correct URL	Displays the Login page	shots=1	PASSED
002	Login/Forgot Password	Click Forgot Password button	Displays the Forgot Password Page	shots=1	PASSED
003	Login/Forgot Password	Click Back to Login button	Displays the Login Page	shots=1	PASSED
004	Login/Forgot Password	Input correct registered email, then click Send Code button	System verifies the email and redirects to the OTP page	shots=1	PASSED
005	Login/Forgot Password	Input correct OTP, then click Verify button	System verifies the OTP and redirects to the reset password page	shots=1	PASSED
006	Login/Forgot Password	Input correct new password format matched with confirm new password, then click Reset Password button	System updates the password in the database and redirects to the login page	shots=1	PASSED
007	Login	Enter the correct email and password, then click Login button	System verifies the account and displays the owner dashboard	shots=1	PASSED
008	Dashboard	Click the Dashboard from the sidebar	Displays the dashboard summary	shots=1	PASSED
009	Schedule Management	Click Schedule Management from the sidebar	Displays the schedule list	shots=1	PASSED
010	Schedule Management	Click View Schedule details	Displays the selected schedule details	shots=1	PASSED
011	Schedule Management/ / Edit Schedule Details	Click Edit Schedule Details button	Displays the edit schedule	shots=1	PASSED
012	Schedule Management/ / Edit Schedule Details	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System updates the schedule details information in the database, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
013	Schedule Management/ / Approve Schedule Entry	Click Approve Schedule Entry button	System approves the schedule entry, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
014	Schedule Management/ / Reject Schedule Entry	Click Reject Schedule Entry button	System rejects the schedule entry, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
015	User Accounts Management/ / Search User Accounts	Input a valid name or email	System searches the database and displays the matching user accounts	shots=1	PASSED
016	User Accounts Management/ / Create User Account	Click Add button	Displays the create user account form	shots=1	PASSED
017	User Accounts Management/ / Create User Account	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System saves the user account information in the database and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
018	User Accounts Management/ / Edit Use Account Details	Click Edit button	Displays the edit user account form	shots=1	PASSED
019	User Accounts Management/ / Edit Use Account Details	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System updates the user account information in the database, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
020	User Accounts Management/ / Deactivate User Account	Click Deactivate User Account button	System deactivates the user account, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
021	User Accounts Management/ / Archive User Account	Click Archive User Account button	System archives the user account, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
022	Patient EMR/ / Patient Profile	Click Patient Profile tab	Displays the selected patient profile	shots=1	PASSED
023	Patient EMR/ / Medical and Dental History	Click Medical and Dental History tab	Displays the selected patient medical and dental history	shots=1	PASSED
024	Patient EMR/ / Treatment History	Click Treatment History tab	Displays the selected patient treatment history	shots=1	PASSED
025	Patient EMR/ / Treatment History	Click Add New Log button	Displays the add new log form	shots=0	
026	Patient EMR/ / Treatment History	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System saves the treatment log in the database, and displays a success message	shots=0	
027	Patient EMR/ / Treatment History	Click Edit Log button	Displays the edit log form	shots=0	
028	Patient EMR/ / Treatment History	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System updates the treatment log in the database, and displays a success message	shots=0	
029	Patient EMR/ / Treatment History	Click Delete Log button	System deletes the treatment log in the database, and displays a success message	shots=0	
030	Patient EMR/ / Digital Odontogram	Click Odontogram tab	Displays the selected patient digital odontogram	shots=1	PASSED
031	Patient EMR/ / Digital Odontogram	Click Edit Odontogram button	Displays the edit odontogram form	shots=0	
032	Patient EMR/ / Digital Odontogram	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System updates the odontogram in the database, and displays a success message	shots=0	
033	Patient EMR/ / Radiograph	Click Radiograph tab	Displays the selected patient X-ray	shots=1	PASSED
034	Patient EMR/ / Radiograph	Click X-ray Images	Display the X-ray summary notes	shots=1	PASSED
035	Material Usage Logging	Click Material Usage Log from the sidebar	Displays the Material Usage Log page	shots=1	PASSED
036	Material Usage Logging	Click Log New Entry button	Displays the material usage entry form	shots=1	PASSED
037	Material Usage Logging	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System saves the material usage entry in the database, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
038	Material Usage Logging	Input a valid procedure or patient name on the search bar	System searches the database and displays matching material usage logs	shots=1	PASSED
039	Material Usage Logging	Click Start Date and End Date filter	Displays the material usage logs from the selected start date up to the selected end date	shots=1	PASSED
040	AI-Assisted Radiograph Review	Click a Radiograph Image	Displays the radiograph image	shots=1	PASSED
041	AI-Assisted Radiograph Review	Click Run Adaptive Enhancement button	System enhances the selected radiograph image and displays a success message	shots=0	
042	AI-Assisted Radiograph Review	Click View Enhanced Image button	Displays the enhanced radiograph image	shots=0	
043	AI-Assisted Radiograph Review	Click View Original button	Displays the original radiograph image	shots=0	
044	AI-Assisted Radiograph Review	Click Generate Summary	System generates an AI summary for the radiograph	shots=0	
045	AI-Assisted Radiograph Review	Click Review AI Summary button	Displays the AI radiograph summary	shots=0	
046	AI-Assisted Radiograph Review	Click Save button	System saves the radiograph summary reviewed by the dentist, and displays a success message	shots=0	
047	AI-Assisted Radiograph Review	Input the correct radiograph findings, then click Save Findings button	System saves the radiograph findings in the database, and displays a success message	shots=0	
048	Branch Management and Expansion Analytics	Click Branch Management from the sidebar	Displays the clinic branches list	shots=1	PASSED
049	Branch Management and Expansion Analytics	Click View Individual Branch Details	Displays the selected branch analytics	shots=1	PASSED
050	Branch Management and Expansion Analytics	Click Edit Branch Details	Displays the edit branch details form	shots=1	PASSED
051	Branch Management and Expansion Analytics	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System updates the branch details in the database, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
052	Supply and Stock Monitoring	Click Supply & Stock Monitoring from the sidebar	Displays the Supply and Stock Monitoring page	shots=1	PASSED
053	Supply and Stock Monitoring	Click View Item Categories List	Displays the item categories list	shots=1	PASSED
054	Supply and Stock Monitoring/ / Update Item Stock Quantity	Click Update Item Stock Quantity button	Displays the edit item stock quantity form	shots=1	PASSED
055	Supply and Stock Monitoring/ / Update Item Stock Quantity	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System updates the item stock quantity information in the database, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
056	Supply and Stock Monitoring/ / Add New Supply Entry	Click Add New Supply Entry button	Displays the create supply entry form	shots=1	PASSED
057	Supply and Stock Monitoring/ / Add New Supply Entry	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System saves the supply entry information in the database, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
058	Supply and Stock Monitoring/ / Edit Item Details	Click Edit Item Details button	Displays the edit item details form	shots=1	PASSED
059	Supply and Stock Monitoring/ / Edit Item Details	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System updates the item details information in the database, and displays a success message	shots=0	
060	Supply and Stock Monitoring	Input a valid item name or code	System searches the database and displays matching supply items	shots=0	
061	Supply and Stock Monitoring	Click the In Stock, Low Stock, or Out of Stock filter	Displays supply items with the selected stock status	shots=0	
062	Branch Transfer Management	Click Transfer Branch button on selected patient	Display branch transfer form	shots=0	
063	Branch Transfer Management	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Transfer button	System updates the branch of the selected patient in the database, and displays a success message	shots=0	
064	Notifications	Click Notifications from the sidebar	Displays the Notification page	shots=1	PASSED
065	Activity Logs	Click Activity Logs from the sidebar	Displays the Activity Logs page	shots=1	PASSED
066	Account Settings/ / View Profile	Click Profile tab	Displays the user profile information	shots=1	PASSED
067	Account Settings/ / Edit Profile	Click Edit Profile button	Displays the edit profile form	shots=1	PASSED
068	Account Settings/ / Edit Profile	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System updates the profile information in the database, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
069	Account Settings/ / Change Password	Click Change Password tab	Displays the Change Password page	shots=1	PASSED
070	Account Settings/ / Change Password	Input the correct current password, new password, and confirm new password, then click Save button	System updates the password in the database, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
071	Login/Sign out	Click �Logout� on the sidebar	System log user out, redirects to login page	shots=1	PASSED

### TABLE 4: Branch Manager / Web Application
001	Login	Enter the correct URL	Displays the Login page	shots=1	PASSED
002	Login/Forgot Password	Click Forgot Password button	Displays the Forgot Password Page	shots=1	PASSED
003	Login/Forgot Password	Click Back to Login button	Displays the Login Page	shots=1	PASSED
004	Login/Forgot Password	Input correct registered email, then click Send Code button	System verifies the email and redirects to the OTP page	shots=1	PASSED
005	Login/Forgot Password	Input correct OTP, then click Verify button	System verifies the OTP and redirects to the reset password page	shots=1	PASSED
006	Login/Forgot Password	Input correct new password format matched with confirm new password, then click Reset Password button	System updates the password in the database and redirects to the login page	shots=1	PASSED
007	Login	Enter the correct email and password, then click Login button	System verifies the account and displays the branch manager dashboard	shots=1	PASSED
008	Dashboard	Click the Dashboard from the sidebar	Displays the dashboard summary	shots=1	PASSED
009	Schedule Management	Click Schedule Management from the sidebar	Displays the schedule list	shots=1	PASSED
010	Schedule Management	Click View Schedule details	Displays the selected schedule details	shots=1	PASSED
011	Schedule Management/ / Edit Schedule Details	Click Edit Schedule Details button	Displays the edit schedule	shots=1	PASSED
012	Schedule Management/ / Edit Schedule Details	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System updates the schedule details information in the database, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
013	Schedule Management/ / Approve Schedule Entry	Click Approve Schedule Entry button	System approves the schedule entry, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
014	Schedule Management/ / Reject Schedule Entry	Click Reject Schedule Entry button	System rejects the schedule entry, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
015	User Accounts Management/ / Search User Accounts	Input a valid name or email	System searches the database and displays the matching user accounts	shots=1	PASSED
016	User Accounts Management/ / Create User Account	Click Add button	Displays the create user account form	shots=0	
017	User Accounts Management/ / Create User Account	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System saves the user account information in the database and displays a success message	shots=0	
018	User Accounts Management/ / Edit Use Account Details	Click Edit button	Displays the edit user account form	shots=1	PASSED
019	User Accounts Management/ / Edit Use Account Details	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System updates the user account information in the database, and displays a success message	shots=0	
020	User Accounts Management/ / Deactivate User Account	Click Deactivate User Account button	System deactivates the user account, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
021	User Accounts Management/ / Archive User Account	Click Archive User Account button	System archives the user account, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
022	Patient EMR/ / Patient Profile	Click Patient Profile tab	Displays the selected patient profile	shots=1	PASSED
023	Patient EMR/ / Medical and Dental History	Click Medical and Dental History tab	Displays the selected patient medical and dental history	shots=1	PASSED
024	Patient EMR/ / Treatment History	Click Treatment History tab	Displays the selected patient treatment history	shots=1	PASSED
025	Patient EMR/ / Treatment History	Click View Treatment Notes	Displays the selected treatment notes	shots=1	PASSED
026	Patient EMR/ / Digital Odontogram	Click Odontogram tab	Displays the selected patient digital odontogram	shots=1	PASSED
027	Patient EMR/ / Radiograph	Click Radiograph tab	Displays the selected patient X-ray	shots=1	PASSED
028	Patient EMR/ / Radiograph	Click X-ray Images	Display the X-ray summary notes	shots=1	PASSED
029	Supply and Stock Monitoring	Click Supply & Stock Monitoring from the sidebar	Displays the Supply and Stock Monitoring page	shots=1	PASSED
030	Supply and Stock Monitoring	Click View Item Categories List	Displays the item categories list	shots=1	PASSED
031	Supply and Stock Monitoring/ / Update Item Stock Quantity	Click Update Item Stock Quantity button	Displays the edit item stock quantity form	shots=0	
032	Supply and Stock Monitoring/ / Update Item Stock Quantity	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System updates the item stock quantity information in the database, and displays a success message	shots=0	
033	Supply and Stock Monitoring/ / Add New Supply Entry	Click Add New Supply Entry button	Displays the create supply entry form	shots=0	
034	Supply and Stock Monitoring/ / Add New Supply Entry	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System saves the supply entry information in the database, and displays a success message	shots=0	
035	Supply and Stock Monitoring/ / Edit Item Details	Click Edit Item Details button	Displays the edit item details form	shots=0	
036	Supply and Stock Monitoring/ / Edit Item Details	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System updates the item details information in the database, and displays a success message	shots=0	
037	Supply and Stock Monitoring	Input a valid item name or code	System searches the database and displays matching supply items	shots=0	
038	Supply and Stock Monitoring	Click the In Stock, Low Stock, or Out of Stock filter	Displays supply items with the selected stock status	shots=0	
039	Branch Transfer Management	Click Transfer Branch button on selected patient	Display branch transfer form	shots=1	PASSED
040	Branch Transfer Management	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Transfer button	System updates the branch of the selected patient in the database, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
041	Notifications	Click Notifications from the sidebar	Displays the Notification page	shots=1	PASSED
042	Activity Logs	Click Activity Logs from the sidebar	Displays the Activity Logs page	shots=1	PASSED
043	Account Settings/ / View Profile	Click Profile tab	Displays the user profile information	shots=1	PASSED
044	Account Settings/ / Edit Profile	Click Edit Profile button	Displays the edit profile form	shots=1	PASSED
045	Account Settings/ / Edit Profile	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System updates the profile information in the database, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
046	Account Settings/ / Change Password	Click Change Password tab	Displays the Change Password page	shots=1	PASSED
047	Account Settings/ / Change Password	Input the correct current password, new password, and confirm new password, then click Save button	System updates the password in the database, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
048	Login/Sign out	Click �Logout� on the sidebar	System log user out, redirects to login page	shots=1	PASSED

### TABLE 5: Dentist / Web Application
001	Login	Enter the correct URL	Displays the Login page	shots=1	PASSED
002	Login/Forgot Password	Click Forgot Password button	Displays the Forgot Password Page	shots=1	PASSED
003	Login/Forgot Password	Click Back to Login button	Displays the Login Page	shots=1	PASSED
004	Login/Forgot Password	Input correct registered email, then click Send Code button	System verifies the email and redirects to the OTP page	shots=1	PASSED
005	Login/Forgot Password	Input correct OTP, then click Verify button	System verifies the OTP and redirects to the reset password page	shots=1	PASSED
006	Login/Forgot Password	Input correct new password format matched with confirm new password, then click Reset Password button	System updates the password in the database and redirects to the login page	shots=1	PASSED
007	Login	Enter the correct email and password, then click Login button	System verifies the account and displays the dentist dashboard	shots=1	PASSED
008	Dashboard	Click the Dashboard from the sidebar	Displays the dashboard summary	shots=1	PASSED
009	Schedule Management	Click Schedule Management from the sidebar	Displays the schedule list	shots=1	PASSED
010	Schedule Management	Click View Schedule details	Displays the selected schedule details	shots=1	PASSED
011	Patient EMR/ / Patient Profile	Click Patient Profile tab	Displays the selected patient profile	shots=1	PASSED
012	Patient EMR/ / Medical and Dental History	Click Medical and Dental History tab	Displays the selected patient medical and dental history	shots=1	PASSED
013	Patient EMR/ / Treatment History	Click Treatment History tab	Displays the selected patient treatment history	shots=1	PASSED
014	Patient EMR/ / Treatment History	Click Add New Log button	Displays the add new log form	shots=1	PASSED
015	Patient EMR/ / Treatment History	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System saves the treatment log in the database, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
016	Patient EMR/ / Treatment History	Click Edit Log button	Displays the edit log form	shots=0	
017	Patient EMR/ / Treatment History	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System updates the treatment log in the database, and displays a success message	shots=0	
018	Patient EMR/ / Treatment History	Click Delete Log button	System deletes the treatment log in the database, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
019	Patient EMR/ / Digital Odontogram	Click Odontogram tab	Displays the selected patient digital odontogram	shots=1	PASSED
020	Patient EMR/ / Digital Odontogram	Click Edit Odontogram button	Displays the edit odontogram form	shots=1	PASSED
021	Patient EMR/ / Digital Odontogram	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System updates the odontogram in the database, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
022	Patient EMR/ / Radiograph	Click Radiograph tab	Displays the selected patient X-ray	shots=1	PASSED
023	Patient EMR/ / Radiograph	Click X-ray Images	Display the X-ray summary notes	shots=1	PASSED
024	Material Usage Logging	Click Material Usage Log from the sidebar	Displays the Material Usage Log page	shots=1	PASSED
025	Material Usage Logging	Click Log New Entry button	Displays the material usage entry form	shots=1	PASSED
026	Material Usage Logging	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System saves the material usage entry in the database, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
027	Material Usage Logging	Input a valid procedure or patient name on the search bar	System searches the database and displays matching material usage logs	shots=1	PASSED
028	Material Usage Logging	Click Start Date and End Date filter	Displays the material usage logs from the selected start date up to the selected end date	shots=1	PASSED
029	AI-Assisted Radiograph Review	Click a Radiograph Image	Displays the radiograph image	shots=1	PASSED
030	AI-Assisted Radiograph Review	Click Run Adaptive Enhancement button	System enhances the selected radiograph image and displays a success message	shots=0	
031	AI-Assisted Radiograph Review	Click View Enhanced Image button	Displays the enhanced radiograph image	shots=0	
032	AI-Assisted Radiograph Review	Click View Original button	Displays the original radiograph image	shots=1	PASSED
033	AI-Assisted Radiograph Review	Click Generate Summary	System generates an AI summary for the radiograph	shots=1	PASSED
034	AI-Assisted Radiograph Review	Click Review AI Summary button	Displays the AI radiograph summary	shots=1	PASSED
035	AI-Assisted Radiograph Review	Click Save button	System saves the radiograph summary reviewed by the dentist, and displays a success message	shots=0	
036	AI-Assisted Radiograph Review	Input the correct radiograph findings, then click Save Findings button	System saves the radiograph findings in the database, and displays a success message	shots=0	
037	Notifications	Click Notifications from the sidebar	Displays the Notification page	shots=1	PASSED
038	Activity Logs	Click Activity Logs from the sidebar	Displays the Activity Logs page	shots=1	PASSED
039	Account Settings/ / View Profile	Click Profile tab	Displays the user profile information	shots=1	PASSED
040	Account Settings/ / Edit Profile	Click Edit Profile button	Displays the edit profile form	shots=1	PASSED
041	Account Settings/ / Edit Profile	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System updates the profile information in the database, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
042	Account Settings/ / Change Password	Click Change Password tab	Displays the Change Password page	shots=1	PASSED
043	Account Settings/ / Change Password	Input the correct current password, new password, and confirm new password, then click Save button	System updates the password in the database, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
044	Login/Sign out	Click �Logout� on the sidebar	System log user out, redirects to login page	shots=1	PASSED

### TABLE 6: Secretary / Web Application
001	Login	Enter the correct URL	Displays the Login page	shots=1	PASSED
002	Login/Forgot Password	Click Forgot Password button	Displays the Forgot Password Page	shots=1	PASSED
003	Login/Forgot Password	Click Back to Login button	Displays the Login Page	shots=1	PASSED
004	Login/Forgot Password	Input correct registered email, then click Send Code button	System verifies the email and redirects to the OTP page	shots=1	PASSED
005	Login/Forgot Password	Input correct OTP, then click Verify button	System verifies the OTP and redirects to the reset password page	shots=1	PASSED
006	Login/Forgot Password	Input correct new password format matched with confirm new password, then click Reset Password button	System updates the password in the database and redirects to the login page	shots=1	PASSED
007	Login	Enter the correct email and password, then click Login button	System verifies the account and displays the secretary dashboard	shots=1	PASSED
008	Dashboard	Click the Dashboard from the sidebar	Displays the dashboard summary	shots=1	PASSED
009	Schedule Management	Click Schedule Management from the sidebar	Displays the schedule list	shots=1	PASSED
010	Schedule Management	Click View Schedule details	Displays the selected schedule details	shots=1	PASSED
011	Schedule Management/ / Edit Schedule Details	Click Edit Schedule Details button	Displays the edit schedule	shots=1	PASSED
012	Schedule Management/ / Edit Schedule Details	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System updates the schedule details information in the database, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
013	Schedule Management/ / Approve Schedule Entry	Click Approve Schedule Entry button	System approves the schedule entry, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
014	Schedule Management/ / Reject Schedule Entry	Click Reject Schedule Entry button	System rejects the schedule entry, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
015	Patient Registration	Click Register New Patient button	Displays the create patient account form	shots=1	PASSED
016	Patient Registration	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System saves the patient account information in the database, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
017	Patient EMR/ / Patient Profile	Click Patient Profile tab	Displays the selected patient profile	shots=1	PASSED
018	Patient EMR/ / Medical and Dental History	Click Medical and Dental History tab	Displays the selected patient medical and dental history	shots=1	PASSED
019	Patient EMR/ / Treatment History	Click Treatment History tab	Displays the selected patient treatment history	shots=1	PASSED
020	Patient EMR/ / Treatment History	Click View Treatment Notes	Displays the selected treatment notes	shots=1	PASSED
021	Patient EMR/ / Digital Odontogram	Click Odontogram tab	Displays the selected patient digital odontogram	shots=1	PASSED
022	Patient EMR/ / Radiograph	Click Radiograph tab	Displays the selected patient X-ray	shots=1	PASSED
023	Patient EMR/ / Radiograph	Click X-ray Images	Display the X-ray summary notes	shots=1	PASSED
024	Notifications	Click Notifications from the sidebar	Displays the Notification page	shots=1	PASSED
025	Activity Logs	Click Activity Logs from the sidebar	Displays the Activity Logs page	shots=1	PASSED
026	Account Settings/ / View Profile	Click Profile tab	Displays the user profile information	shots=1	PASSED
027	Account Settings/ / Edit Profile	Click Edit Profile button	Displays the edit profile form	shots=1	PASSED
028	Account Settings/ / Edit Profile	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System updates the profile information in the database, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
029	Account Settings/ / Change Password	Click Change Password tab	Displays the Change Password page	shots=1	PASSED
030	Account Settings/ / Change Password	Input the correct current password, new password, and confirm new password, then click Save button	System updates the password in the database, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
031	Login/Sign out	Click �Logout� on the sidebar	System log user out, redirects to login page	shots=1	PASSED

### TABLE 7: Patient / Web Application
001	Website Booking	Click Appointment tab	Displays the website appointment booking form	shots=1	PASSED
002	Website Booking	Input all appointment fields completely and in the correct format, then click Book Appointment button	System saves the website booking in the database, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
003	Login	Enter the correct URL	Displays the Login page	shots=1	PASSED
004	Login/Forgot Password	Click Forgot Password button	Displays the Forgot Password Page	shots=1	PASSED
005	Login/Forgot Password	Click Back to Login button	Displays the Login Page	shots=1	PASSED
006	Login/Forgot Password	Input correct registered email, then click Send Code button	System verifies the email and redirects to the OTP page	shots=1	PASSED
007	Login/Forgot Password	Input correct OTP, then click Verify button	System verifies the OTP and redirects to the reset password page	shots=1	PASSED
008	Login/Forgot Password	Input correct new password format matched with confirm new password, then click Reset Password button	System updates the password in the database and redirects to the login page	shots=1	PASSED
009	Login	Enter the correct email and password, then click Login button	System verifies the account and displays the patient dashboard	shots=1	PASSED
010	Dashboard	Click the Dashboard from the sidebar	Displays the dashboard summary	shots=1	PASSED
011	Appointment Scheduling	Click Book Appointment button	Displays the appointment booking form	shots=1	PASSED
012	Appointment Scheduling	Input all appointment fields completely and in the correct format, then click Book Appointment button	System saves the appointment in the database, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
013	Appointment Scheduling	Click Reschedule Appointment button	Displays the appointment rescheduling form	shots=1	PASSED
014	Appointment Scheduling	Input the new appointment schedule, then click Reschedule button	System updates the appointment schedule in the database and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
015	Appointment Scheduling	Click Cancel Appointment button	Displays the appointment cancellation form	shots=1	PASSED
016	Appointment Scheduling	Input the valid reason for cancellation, then click Cancel Schedule button	System cancels the appointment in the database, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
017	Patient EMR/ / Patient Profile	Click Patient Profile tab	Displays the selected patient profile	shots=1	PASSED
018	Patient EMR/ / Medical and Dental History	Click Medical and Dental History tab	Displays the selected patient medical and dental history	shots=1	PASSED
019	Patient EMR/ / Treatment History	Click Treatment History tab	Displays the selected patient treatment history	shots=1	PASSED
020	Patient EMR/ / Treatment History	Click View Treatment Notes	Displays the selected treatment notes	shots=1	PASSED
021	Patient EMR/ / Digital Odontogram	Click Odontogram tab	Displays the selected patient digital odontogram	shots=1	PASSED
022	Patient EMR/ / Radiograph	Click Radiograph tab	Displays the selected patient X-ray	shots=1	PASSED
023	Patient EMR/ / Radiograph	Click X-ray Images	Display the X-ray summary notes	shots=1	PASSED
024	Patient EMR	Click Export PDF button	System downloads the patient profile PDF	shots=1	PASSED
025	AI Patient Engagement/ / NgitiBot	Click NgitiBot floating button	Displays the NgitiBot conversation window	shots=1	PASSED
026	AI Patient Engagement/ / NgitiBot	Input a patient care question, then click Send button	System processes the question and displays the NgitiBot response	shots=1	PASSED
027	AI Patient Engagement/ / Dental Health Education	Click Dental Health Education button	Displays the dental health educational materials	shots=1	PASSED
028	AI Patient Engagement/ / Oral Health Management	Click Oral Health Management button	Displays the Oral Health Management page	shots=1	PASSED
029	AI Patient Engagement/ / Oral Health Management	Click Log Today button	Displays the log today form	shots=1	PASSED
030	AI Patient Engagement/ / Oral Health Management	Input the daily log, then click Add Daily Log button	System saves the daily log in the database, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
031	AI Patient Engagement/ / Predictive Visit	Click Predictive Visit button	Displays the dentist-recommended visit or AI-generated recommendations for the next visit	shots=0	
032	Notifications	Click Notifications from the sidebar	Displays the Notification page	shots=1	PASSED
033	Activity Logs	Click Activity Logs from the sidebar	Displays the Activity Logs page	shots=1	PASSED
034	Account Settings/ / View Profile	Click Profile tab	Displays the user profile information	shots=1	PASSED
035	Account Settings/ / Edit Profile	Click Edit Profile button	Displays the edit profile form	shots=1	PASSED
036	Account Settings/ / Edit Profile	Input all fields completely and in the correct format, then click Save button	System updates the profile information in the database, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
037	Account Settings/ / Change Password	Click Change Password tab	Displays the Change Password page	shots=1	PASSED
038	Account Settings/ / Change Password	Input the correct current password, new password, and confirm new password, then click Save button	System updates the password in the database, and displays a success message	shots=1	PASSED
039	Login/Sign out	Click �Logout� on the sidebar	System log user out, redirects to login page	shots=1	PASSED
